They’re Dynamite
Johnny Eager is a crime, drama film directed by Mervyn LeRoy.
A charming racketeer seduces the DA's stepdaughter
for revenge, then falls in love.
Johnny Eager, played by Robert Taylor.
Lisbeth Bard, played by Lana Turner.
John Benson Farrell, played by Edward Arnold.
Jeff Hartnett, played by Van Heflin.
Jimmy Courtney, played by Robert Sterling.
Garnet, played by Patricia Dane.
Johnny Eager is a 1941 American film noir directed by Mervyn LeRoy and
starring Robert Taylor, Lana Turner and Van Heflin.
Heflin won an Academy Award for Best Supporting Actor.
The film was one of many spoofed in Dead Men Don't Wear Plaid (1982).
The film explores themes of self sacrifice, gambling,
staged death, gangster, taxi driver.
The tone is dark and emotional.